# Jeffrey Lu

Full-Stack developer, with a background in shipping and logistics. I bring my experience of notable attention to detail, partaking in handling moving parts through production. I relish in the satisfaction of a completed project and patience that comes with it. Combining these experiences, I hope to create more ease of access applications for people across the globe.

**SKILLS** 

JavascriptMongoDBHerokuHTMLSQLGitCSSPythonSQL

React.js Django Node.js Express.js

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **General Assembly**

MARCH 2022 - MAY 2022

Designed user facing projects utilizing Javascript and React.js

Built back-end website applications, and setup databases using MongoDB, SQL, with other frameworks.

Experience in working in small teams for building acceptable products within allotted deadlines.

## **Apex Logistics International** — Ocean Imports Team Lead

JULY 2018 - 2021

Extensive knowledge on the process of importing goods into the United States.

Provided cross country shipping solutions to ensure client's distribution deadlines are met.

Dangerous Goods handling certified

## **Apex Logistics International** — Ocean Imports Coordinator

AUGUST 2016 - JUNE 2018

### **EDUCATION**

**General Assembly**— *Software Engineer Immersive* 

MARCH 2022 - MAY 2022

New York City College of Technology

AUGUST 2009 - JUNE 2011

Studied Electrical Engineering

# **Brooklyn Technical High School**

AUGUST 2005 - JUNE 2009

Majored in architecture

#### **CONTACT INFO**

(718) 415-8521 lu.jeffrey91@gmail.com

Linked-In Github